{
    "subject": "resource/Frank_Miller_(Medal_of_Honor)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Soldier",
    "human_readable": "Frank Miller (Medal of Honor) is a Soldier.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9653151631355286,
            "question": "Is Frank Miller a soldier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7246260046958923,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Frank Miller's profession and his Medal of Honor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6829303503036499,
            "question": "For what achievement did Frank Miller receive the Medal of Honor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6814605593681335,
            "question": "Who is Frank Miller?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6020998358726501,
            "question": "Name someone who received the Medal of Honor."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5111212134361267,
            "question": "Who received the Medal of Honor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4666215181350708,
            "question": "What is Frank Miller's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40136533975601196,
            "question": "What does it mean to be a soldier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20774692296981812,
            "question": "What are some examples of acts that might earn someone the Medal of Honor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11376486718654633,
            "question": "What is the name of the highest military decoration in the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frank Miller (Medal of Honor) is a Soldier.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2812_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of acts that might earn someone the Medal of Honor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2812_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does it mean to be a soldier?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2812_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Frank Miller's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2812_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2812_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as there are multiple mentions of Frank Miller's career as a military officer and his receiving the Medal of Honor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Frank Miller's military career, including his service as a soldier and receiving the Medal of Honor. Therefore, the statement \"Frank Miller (Medal of Honor) is a Soldier\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Frank Miller (Medal of Honor) is not a soldier. He served in the United States Army during the Vietnam War and was awarded the Medal of Honor, but he later became a command sergeant major and a benefits counselor for the Veterans Administration, which are military roles associated with the enlisted rank structure, not officers or soldiers.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}